我记起来了  我是天使
I remember now. I'm an angel.
我被判处了死刑
I have a death sentence on my head.
-为什么  - 我堕落了
- Why? - I disobeyed.
你真的不该来
You really shouldn't have come.
你必须阻止这一切
You have to stop it.
阻止什么
Stop what?
1973年
1973.
妈妈
Mom?
我是约翰·温彻斯特
John Winchester.
我的父母是玛丽和约翰·温彻斯特
My parents are Mary and John winchester.
我是你的孙子
And I am your grandson.
玛丽1983年被黄眼恶魔杀害了
Mary gets killed by a yellow-eyed demon in 1983.
如果我们现在不杀了他
Now, if we don't catch this thing now and kill it
他一旦逃跑  玛丽就死定了
And it gets away... then Mary dies.
不
No!
我什么都没能阻止  她还是做了交易
I couldn't stop any of it. She still made the deal.
她还是死在了婴儿房  对吗
She still died in the nursery, didn't she?
天意不可违  迪恩
Destiny can't be changed, Dean.
殊途同归
All roads lead to the same destination.
我愿得偿  我爱恶魔
Oh, I take it all back. I love the devil.
这才是世界和平啊
Now, that's what I call peace on earth.
安娜
Anna?
我  我是在工作呢
I was just, uh, working on a case.
这就是你梦到的
This is what you dream about.
尴尬
This is awkward.
为什么你要进入我的意识
Why are you gate-crashing my head?
为什么不直接在旅馆现身
Why don't you just swing by the motel?
我找不到你
I can't find you.
卡西做的好事
Oh. Cass did this thing.
卡西  很好
Cass. Right.
你现在倒有个能指望的朋友了
Now, there's a friend you can count on.
什么
What?
他没告诉你吗
He didn't tell you?
告诉我什么
Tell me what?
我去了哪里
Where I've been.
当然不会了  他何必呢
Of course not. Why would he?
你到哪儿去了
Where have you been?
监牢
Prison.
上面的
Upstairs.
无休无止的折磨  老生常谈的伪善
All the torture, twice the self-righteousness.
他为什么不告诉我们你去哪了
Why wouldn't he have told us where you were?
因为这是拜他所赐
'cause he's the one who turned me in.
别这么惊讶
Don't look so shocked.
他一直是个好卒子
He was always a good little soldier.
绝对唯命是从
Did anything under orders.
我不知道  你还好吗
I didn't know. Are you okay?
不  我没多少时间了
No. And I don't have long.
我越狱了
I broke out --
差点没成功
Barely.
他们在通缉我
They're looking for me.
如果被发现
If they find me --
你要我做什么
Okay. What do you need?
来见我  225号工厂
Meet me. 225 industrial.
拜托了  要尽快
And, please, just hurry.
有人吗
Hello?
谁在那儿
Who's there?
你好  安娜
Hello, Anna.
如果不是这么了解你
If I didn't know any better...
我会以为是温彻斯特不信任我
I'd say the Winchester don't trust me.
他们信  但我不
They do. I don't.
我不会让他们来的
I wouldn't let them come.
为什么这么做
And why is that?
如果你能越狱  那是因为他们故意放你走
If you're out of prison, it's because they let you out.
让你来做那个黑手
And they sent you here to do their dirty work.
你凭什么这么肯定
And what makes you so sure?
因为我也曾经历过天堂的劝诫
Because I've experienced... heaven's persuasion.
你是指把我交给他们吗
You mean when you gave me to them.
那是个失误
That was a mistake.
安娜  不论他们送你来做什么
Anna, whatever they sent you here to do --
不是他们送我来  我逃跑了
They didn't send me. I escaped.
没人能逃脱
No one escapes.
都这么多世纪了  你现在开始低估我吗
All these centuries, and you're underestimating me now?
如果你不是他们那边的  你想要什么
If you're not one of them, then what do you want?
我想要帮你们
I want to help.
-你要帮忙  - 是的
- You want to help? - Yes.
那你想用那把刀做什么
Then what are doing with that knife?
我不能保护自己吗
I'm not allowed to defend myself?
对抗谁  那把刀根本伤不了天使
Against whom? That blade doesn't work against angels.
不像这一把
It's not like this one.
可能你不是在给上面干活
Maybe you're not working for heaven.
但你对我一定有所隐瞒
But there's something you're not telling me.
萨姆·温彻斯特必须得死
Sam Winchester has to die.
我很抱歉  但是我们别无选择
I am sorry. But we have no choice.
他是路西法的皮囊
He's Lucifer's vessel.
-他不是唯一的皮囊  - 什么  那个叫尼克的男人吗
- He's not the only one. - What? That guy Nick?
我们说话的当儿他正在灰飞烟灭
He's burning away as we speak.
他不行
No.
萨姆才是最重要的那个皮囊
Sam is the only vessel that matters.
你知道那意味着什么
You know what that means.
如果路西法得不到萨姆
If Lucifer can't take Sam,
他的整个计划就破灭了
his whole plan short-circuits.
没有和米迦勒的决战  也没有恶魔病毒
No fight with Michael, no croatoan virus,
骑士们也得乖乖地回去坚守岗位
The horsemen go back to their day jobs.
就算你可以  杀了萨姆
Even if you could... kill Sam,
撒旦还是会让他复活的
Satan would just bring him back to life.
如果我把他的细胞驱散到横跨整个宇宙
Not after I scatter his cells
那他就没法子了
across the universe.
他们永远找不到他  找不到完整的他
They'll never find him -- not all of him.
会有别的办法的
We'll find another way.
那你们进展如何
How's that going?
科尔特效果怎么样  还有上帝找到了吗
How's the colt working out? Or the search for god?
这些办法都有用吗
Is anything working?
如果你想阻止恶魔的话  只能如此
If you want to stop the devil, this is how.
我还是不会答应
The answer is still no.
因为萨姆是我的朋友
Because Sam is my friend.
你变了
You've changed.
也许为时已晚
Maybe too late.
不过我确实变了
But I have.
安娜  我们曾经一起经历过很多事
Anna, we've been through much together.
可如果你想加害于萨姆·温彻斯特
But you come near Sam Winchester,
我也不会放过你
and I'll kill you.
老天
Oh, my god.
-老天  - 嘿
- Oh, my god. - Hey.
-老天啊  - 你没事吧
- Oh, my god. - Hey. You okay?
我们得把她送到医院去  来
We have to get her to a hospital. Come on.
真的吗  安娜
Really? Anna?
-我不相信  - 是真的
- I don't believe it. - It's true.
这么说她开始走格伦·克洛斯范儿了(电影演员)
So she's gone all Glenn Close, huh?
棒极了
That's awesome.
谁是格伦·克洛斯
Who's Glenn Close?
谁也不是
No one.
只是个喜欢煮兔子  神经有问题的贱人
Just this psycho bitch who likes to boil rabbits.
那么  那个要杀了我的计划
So, t-the -- the plan to kill me --
真的可以阻止撒旦吗
would it actually stop Satan?
怎么会  萨姆  拜托
No, Sam, come on.
卡西  你怎么想  安娜说的有道理吗
Cass, what do you think? Does Anna have a point?
没有
No.
她是  格伦·克洛斯
She's a... "Glenn Close."
我不懂
I don't get it.
我们干嘛要找一个想灭掉萨姆的小妞儿
We're looking for the chick that wants to gank Sam?
干嘛自找麻烦
Why poke the bear?
安娜会不断尝试
Anna will keep trying.
除非萨姆死了  否则她不会放弃的
She won't give up until Sam is dead.
所以我们先下手为强
So we kill her first.
[咒语]
-我找到她了  - 她在哪儿
- I found her. - Where is she?
不是地点的问题
Not where.
是时间的问题
When.
她在1978年
It's 1978.
什么
What?
她在1978年干什么  我都还没出生呢
Why 1978? I wasn't even born yet.
如果她杀了你父母  也就没有你了
You won't be... if she kills your parents.
什么
What?
因为我在  安娜伤不到你
Anna can't get to you because of me.
所以她要去找你们的父母
So she's going after them.
马上送我们回去
Take us back right now.
这相当于让你们羊入虎口
And deliver you right to Anna?
我一个人去
I should go alone.
他们是我们的父母  卡西  我们要去
They're our parents, Cass. We're going.
不是这么容易的
It's not that easy.
-为什么  - 就算我可以使用荣光的力量
- Why not? - Time travel was difficult
时间穿梭也是很困难的
even with the powers of heaven at my disposal.
可你堕天了
But you're cut off.
所以你就像是少了燃料的跑车是吗
So what? You're like a Delorean without enough plutonium?
我不懂那个比喻什么意思
I don't understand that reference.
但我想说的是
But I'm telling you,
携带其他人一起进行时间穿梭依旧会
taking this trip, with passengers, no less...
削弱我的力量
...it'll weaken me.
他们是我们的爸妈
They're our mom and dad.
如果我们能救他们
If we can save them,
不单是不让安娜伤害他们
and not just from Anna --
我是说  如果我们能阻止这场战争
I mean, if we can set things right...
我们必须试试
we have to try.
准备好了吗
Ready?
凑合吧
Not really.
弯曲膝盖
Bend your knees.
我们成功了吗
Did we make it?
除非是他们再产品拓车了
Unless they're bringing pintos back into production,
看来  我们是成功了
I, uh, I'd say yes.
卡西
Cass?
放轻松  放轻松  你没事吧
Take it easy. Take it easy. You all right?
我没事
I'm fine.
比我预想的要好多了
I'm much better than I expected.
卡西
Cass!
还有呼吸  虽然比较微弱
He's breathing... sort of.
我们怎么办
What do we do?
我说  光是看到那胡子
I mean, the mustaches alone...
我给卡西付了
So I paid for Cass for
5个晚上的房费  蜜月套房
five nights up in the, uh, honeymoon suite.
我告诉经理  不论如何都不许打扰
I told the manager, "Do not disturb no matter what."
知道他跟我说什么吗
You know what he said to me?
好  别担心  想买点内幕消息吗
"Yeah. Don't sweat it. Want to buy some dope?"
"内幕"唉
Dope.
我们应该在附近逛逛
We ought to stick around here,
然后买点微软公司的股份
buy some stock in Microsoft.
如果卡西无法恢复的话
Yeah, we might have to
估计我们真得买股份去了
if Cass doesn't recover.
他没事吧
Is he all right?
难道我看起来像天使医生或是护士小妞吗
What do I look like -- Dr. Angel, medicine woman?
他自会醒来的
He'll wake up.
他  可是个非常坚韧又带翅膀的臭小子
He's, you know, tough for a little nerdy dude with wings.
如果他都搞成这样子
If he landed like that,
希望安娜也好不到哪去
hopefully, so did Anna.
至少我们能赢得一点时间
Should buy us some time.
那么  你找到他们了吗
So, did you find 'em?
当然  温切斯特家  知更树街485号
Yeah. Uh...The Winchesters. 485 Robin tree.
直接去会会咱爸妈吧
Let's go pop in on the folks.
萨姆  萨姆  等等  等一下
Sam. Sam. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
迪恩  安娜可能随时出现
Dean, Anna could be here any second.
我们究竟该怎么进去  怎么和他们说呢
What exactly are we gonna march up there and tell 'em?
说实话
Uh, the truth.
什么  难道说他们的儿子从未来回来
What, that their sons are back from the future?
是为了从天使终结者手中挽救他们吗
To save them from an angel gone "Terminator"?
拜托  这年代那种电影还没出现呐
Come on. Those movies haven't even come out yet.
那  就告诉她恶魔要抓他们
Well, then tell her demons are after 'em.
她认为你是个猎人  不是吗
I mean, she thinks you're a hunter, right?
是  一个她老爸一死就立马消失了的猎人
Yeah, a hunter who disappeared right when her dad died.
她肯定爱死我了
She's gonna love me.
你就跟着我吧
Just follow my lead.
今天工作怎么样
How was work?
挺  好的
It was, uh, great.
先去洗手
Ah! Not until you wash up.
真是爱死你发号施令的时候了
I love when you get bossy.
嘿  玛丽
Hi, Mary.
你不能来这里
You can't be here.
抱歉如果来得不是时候的话
I'm sorry if this is a bad time.
你不明白  我已经不再
You don't understand. I'm not...
我洗手不干了
I don't do that anymore.
我现在拥有平凡的生活  你们该走了
I have a normal life now. You have to go.
抱歉  但这很重要  明白吗
I'm sorry, but this is important, okay?
不好意思  亲爱的  他们只不过是
Sorry, sweetie, they're just...
玛丽的表兄弟
Mary's cousins.
我们路过这儿一定
Yeah, we couldn't stop through town
要来跟她打声招呼的  不是吗
without swinging by and saying "Hey," Now, could we?
迪恩
Dean.
你很眼熟啊
You look familiar.
是吗
Really?
是啊  你也挺眼熟的  老实说
Yeah, you do, too, actually, you know?
我们一定见过面的
We must have met sometime.
在某个小镇  对吗  爱上那些小镇了
Small towns, right? Got to love them.
约翰
I'm John.
这是萨姆
This is Sam.
萨姆  玛丽的父亲也叫萨姆
Sam. Uh, Mary's father was a Sam.
哦  他这是个姓
Uh, it's a -- it's a family name.
你没事吧  伙计  你似乎有点吓着了
You okay, pal? You look a little spooked.
噢  没事  没事的
Oh. Oh, yeah.
只不过是  旅行得太久了
Just a...long trip.
好了  萨姆和迪恩正要继续他们的旅程
Well, Sam and Dean were just on their way out.
什么  他们才刚到这儿呢
What? They just got here.
真高兴有机会见到玛丽那边的亲戚
Real happy to meet folks from Mary's side.
请进来喝杯啤酒吧
Please come on in for a beer.
正合我意
Twist my arm.
你确实没事吗  萨姆
Are you sure you're okay, Sam?
当然  当然  我只是
Yeah, yeah. Um, I'm just, um...
你真是太漂亮了
You are so beautiful.
他的意思是通常的
He means that in a-a non-weird,
健康的  对家人的赞美
wholesome, family kind of a way.
是的  没错
Yeah, right.
我们已经  有很长一段时间没见玛丽了
We haven't seen Mary in -- in quite some time, and --
她简直和我们的妈妈一摸一样
See, she's the spitting image of our mom.
那种感觉  非常  非常可怕
I mean, it's -- it's -- Eerie.
你们是什么关系呢
So, how are you guys related?
应该是  远亲
You know, uh, distantly.
所以  你们认识玛丽的父母了
Oh. So you knew Mary's parents?
是的  没错  没错
Yeah. Yeah, yeah.
玛丽的爸爸
Mary's dad was, uh...
曾像祖父一般疼我们
pretty much like a grandpa to us.
遗憾的是  他因心脏病发过世了
That was tragic -- that heart attack.
是的  太遗憾了
Yes, it was.
对了  你们进城是要做什么呢
So, uh, what are you guys doing in town, anyway?
接了点儿活要干
Uh, business, you know.
是吗  什么样的工作
Oh, yeah? What line of work?
-修管道  - 回收废金属
- Plumbing. - Scrap metal.
天啊  都快7点了
Oh, gosh. It's almost 7:00.
我不想无礼的  但必须得去作晚餐了
I hate to be rude, but I got to get dinner ready.
也许他们可以留下来
Maybe they could stay.
我肯定他们得走
I'm sure they have to leave.
听着  请留下来吧
Uh, look, please stay.
这对我而言很有意义
You know, it would mean a lot to me.
我  我没怎么和玛丽的家人见过面
I-I haven't met much of mary's side of the family.
真的  伍德森先生  我求你再考虑考虑
Look, Mr. Woodson, I'm begging you to reconsider.
我也想  约翰  你是个出色的机械师
I'd like to, John. You're a great mechanic.
但时下局面确实不好
But times ain't exactly rosy.
兼职也行  我真的很需要这份工作
E-even just part time. I really need this job.
好吧  你现在马上过来  我们谈谈
All right, look. Come on in right now, let's talk.
也许我们可以找到双赢的途径
Maybe we can figure something out.
真的吗
You serious?
十分钟之内来见我  别让我等太久
I'll see you in 10 minutes. Don't keep me waiting.
你们必须离开  马上
You have to leave. Now.
-好的  听我说  - 不  你们听着
- Okay, just listen - No, you listen.
上次我见到你  我父母就被恶魔杀了
Last time I saw you, a demon killed my parents.
现在你俩来找我还轻松地说成是家人
Now you waltz in here like you're family?
无论你想干吗  都不可能  离我远点
Whatever you want -- no. Leave me alone.
你和约翰有危险
You and John are in danger.
什么意思
What are you talking about?
有东西来追杀你们
Something's coming for you.
恶魔
Demon?
-不是  - 那是什么
- Not exactly. - Well, what, then?
很难解释  好吧
It's kind of hard to explain, okay? It's -- it's --
一个天使
An angel.
什么
What?
-世上没这种东西  - 我也希望
- There's no such thing. - I wish.
它比恶魔强大一倍  也更烦人
But they're twice as strong as demons...and bigger dicks.||
为什么天使要来杀我们
Why would an angel want to kill us?
说来话长  我们过会儿告诉你
It's a long story, and we'll tell you the whole thing,
但是现在  你要相信我们  然后马上出发
But right now, you've got to trust us, and we got to go.
你看我像是说谎的样子吗
Look at my face and tell me if I'm lying to you.
好吧
Okay.
-我们去哪儿  - 离开这里  马上
- Where do we go? - Out of here. We got to move now, though.
好吧  但我怎么跟约翰说
Okay. But what do I tell john?
就说
Just tell him --
约翰
John?
伍德森先生
Mr. Woodson?
你还在吗
You still here?
安娜  见到你我真想说很高兴
I wish I could say it's good to see you, Anna.
我也是  迪恩
You too, Dean.
对不住了
I'm sorry.
不好意思
Sorry.
天使可不是那么容易被搞定的
It's not that easy to kill an angel.
是的  但你可以把他们送走
No. But you can distract 'em.
怪物
Monsters.
Monsters?
是的
Yes.
怪物真的存在
Monsters are real.
对不起  我不知道怎么
I'm sorry, I didn't know how --
你们猎杀怪物  三个都是吗
and you fight them? All of you?
是的
Yeah.
有多久了
How long?
我一生都是
All my life.
-约翰  我有我的苦衷  - 她身不由己
- John, just try to understand -- - She didn't exactly have a choice --
闭嘴  都闭嘴
Shut up, all of you!
别再说了  拜托
Look, not another word, or so help me,
不然我就掉头开回去
I will turn this car around!
真是一次尴尬的全家公路旅行
Wow. Awkward family road trip.
别讲笑了
No kidding.
这地方一直是我们家的
Place has been in the family for years.
恶魔陷阱
Devil's trap.
纯铁制装修
Pure iron fixtures, of course.
储藏室里应该有盐和圣水
Um, there should be salt and holy water in the pantry,
还有刀和枪
Knives, guns.
这些只能赶走它
All that stuff will do is piss it off.
那怎么才能杀它  或至少拖点时间
So, what will kill it? Or slow it down, at least?
这些作用不大
Not much.
很好
Great.
他只是说作用不大  不是没作用
He said not much, not nothing.
我们有家伙
We packed.
把这个东西画出来
If we put this up...
如果她靠近
And she comes close,
我们就能把她送到星际飞船上去
We beam her right off the starship.
这个是圣油
This is holy oil.
就好像是  天使的"恶魔陷阱"
It's kind of like a -- like a devil's trap for angels.
来吧  我来演示一下
Come on. I'll show you how it works.
那纸上的东西有什么用
Hey, what's the deal with the thing on the paper?
是符咒  意思是
It's a sigil. That means --
我不管它什么意思  要把它画哪儿
I don't care what it means. Where does it go?
墙上或者门上
On a wall or a door.
要画多大
How big should I make it?
约翰
John...
怎么了
What?
你们可能都把我当傻瓜一样
Y'all might have treated me like a fool,
但我不是个废物
But I am not useless.
我可以画一个该死的  叫什么  魔印
I can draw a damn... whatever it is -- a sigil.
不如你去帮萨姆那边
Why don't you go help Sam out?
因为这需要
Okay, 'cause this has got to be done in...
用人血来画
It's got to be done in human blood.
要画多大
So, how big?
好吧  告诉你
I'll show you.
笑什么
What?
这一瞬间  你让我想起了我的父亲
All of a sudden, you -- you really remind me of my dad.
画得不错
That's really good.
你是来检查作业的吗
You come to check on me?
我想说  我感到很抱歉
I wanted to say I-I'm sorry about all this.
对所有的这一切
I-I know it's a lot.
你们知道这些猎杀恶魔的事多久了
Look, how long have you known about this... hunting stuff?
从一开始就知道
Pretty much forever.
我爸爸就是这样把我带大的
My dad raised me in it.
真的假的
You're serious?
谁他妈的会这样对一个小孩
Who the hell does that to a kid?
据我所知  玛丽的爸妈就是如此
Well, I mean, for the record, mary's parents did.
我不管
I don't care.
怎样的一个不负责任的混蛋
You know, what kind of irresponsible bastard
会让一孩子面对
Lets a child anywhere near --
你可能会没命的
Y-you know, you could've been killed!
我也差点儿就呜呼了
I, uh... came kind of close.
应该是不止一次
The number it must've done on your head...
你父亲理应保护你
Your father was supposed to protect you.
他尽力了
He was trying.
竭尽全力
He died trying.
相信我
Believe me...
我曾经生他的气
I used to be mad at him.
我是说曾经
I-I mean, I used to...
我曾经恨过他
I used to hate the guy.
但现在
But now I-I...
我懂了
I get it.
他已经尽了全力
He was...just doing the best he could.
他努力坚持下去
And he was trying to keep it together
即使是在那种不可能的情况下
In -- in -- in this impossible situation.
知道吗
See...
我妈妈
My mom, um...
她神奇  美丽
She was amazing, beautiful,
她是他一生的挚爱
And... she was the love of his life.
她被杀了
And she got killed.
我想
And...I think
他什么也不做的话  是会疯掉的
He would have gone crazy if he didn't do
something.
事实上是
Truth is, um...
我爸爸死了
My dad died
我还没来得及告诉他
Before I got to tell him that...
我理解
...I understand...
他所做所为的原因
...why he did what he did.
我原谅他以前对我们做过的事情
And I forgive him for what it did to us.
真的
I do.
我
And I just --
我爱他
I love him.
尤利尔
Uriel.
-你看上去不错  - 你不应该召唤我
- You look well. - You shouldn't have
called.
我们被严令禁止下到这里来
We're under strict orders not to come
down here,
更不用说带着皮囊了
Much less take a vessel.
你不是现在的安娜
You're not the Anna of now.
是的  但是30年后的安娜还是你的上级
No, but 30 years from now, I'm still your
superior.
我要你杀几个人类
I need you to kill some humans.
我总是乐意去毁灭
Always happy to do some smiting.
发生了什么
But what's going on?
在未来  这些人会杀了你  尤利尔
In the future, these people are going to
kill you, Uriel.
我现在给你机会先杀了他们
I'm giving you the chance to kill them
first.
谢谢
Thank you.
好的
Okay.
你说过有空的时候就给我们解释这一切
You said you'd explain everything when we
had a minute.
现在我们有空了
We have a minute.
为什么天使想让我死
Why does an angel want me dead?
因为他们是混蛋
'Cause they're dicks.
这个解释不够好
Not good enough.
我甚至都不知道他们的存在  现在我是靶子了
I didn't even know they existed, and now
I'm a target?
这个挺复杂
It's complicated.
好吧
Fine.
洗耳恭听
All ears.
你要相信我  好吗
You're just gonna have to trust me, okay?
我一直相信你
I've been trusting you all day.
有点难以置信
It's kind of hard to believe.
好吧  我走了
All right, then. I'm walking out the
door.
我是你儿子
I'm your son.
什么
What?
我是你儿子
I'm your son.
不好意思  我不知道还能怎么说
Sorry. I don't know how else to say it.
我们来自2010年
We're from the year 2010.
一个天使把我们瞬移到这里
An angel zapped us back here...
不是攻击你的那个  而是个友好的天使
Not the one that attacked you --
friendlier.
你别指望我会相信这些
You can't expect me to believe that.
我们的名字是迪恩和萨姆·温彻斯特
Our names are Dean and Sam winchester.
是以你父母的名字来命名的
We're named after your parents.
当我生病的时候
When I would get sick,
你会给我做番茄米汤
You would make me tomato-rice soup,
因为这是你妈妈给你做过的
Because that's what your mom made you.
你不给我们唱摇篮曲
And instead of a lullaby...
而是唱"Hey Jude"
You would sing "Hey Jude"...
因为这首是你最喜欢的披头士的歌曲
...'cause that's your favorite beatles
song.
我
I...
我不相信
I don't believe it.
不
No.
对不起  但这都是真的
I'm sorry, but it's true.
我把我的孩子培养成了猎魔人
I raised my kids to be hunters?
不  你没有
No. No, you didn't.
我怎么能那样对你们
How could I do that to you?
你没有那样做
You didn't do it...
因为你死了
...because you're dead.
什么  发生什么了
What? What happened?
黄眼恶魔
Yellow-eyed demon.
他杀了你
He killed you, and...
约翰成了猎魔人为你报仇
...John became a hunter to get revenge.
他把我们养大的
He raised us in this life.
听我说
Listen to me.
一个恶魔进入了山姆的婴儿房
A demon comes into Sam's nursery
在他刚满6个月的时候
Exactly six months after he's born --
1983年11月2日
November 2, 1983.
记住这个日期
Remember that date.
无论你做什么
And whatever you do...
不要进去
Do not go in there.
那个早晨  你要醒来带上山姆快跑
You wake up that morning and you take Sam
and you run.
这个方法不够好  迪恩
That's not good enough, Dean.
不管她跑去哪里  那个恶魔都会找到她
Wherever she goes, the demon's gonna find
her...
还有我
Find me.
好吧  那你说怎么办
Well, then what?
她可以离开爸爸  那才是解决办法
She can leave dad. That's what.
你必须离开约翰
You got to leave John.
什么
What?
当这一切过去以后  请离开
When this is all over, walk away...
再也别回来
And never look back.
那样我们就不会出生了  他说的对
So we're never born. He's right.
我...我不能
I-I can't.
你们告诉我你们是我的孩子
You're saying that you're my children,
然后你们又说...
And now you're saying --
你没有别的选择
You have no other choice.
没有出生过和死掉相比
There's a big difference between
是有很大区别的
dying and never being born.
相信我  我们无所谓的
And trust me, we're okay with it,
我向你保证
I promise you that.
但是我不同意
Okay, well, I'm not.
听我说  你觉得你可以过上渴望已久的
Listen, you think you can have that normal life
正常人生活  但是你做不到的
that you want so bad... but you can't.
很抱歉
I'm sorry.
事情将会变得一团糟
It's all gonna go rotten.
你将会死掉
You are gonna die,
而你的孩子们将会被诅咒
And your children will be cursed.
一定  一定还有别的办法的
There -- there has to be a way.
没有  这是唯一的办法
No, this is the way.
离开约翰
Leave John.
我做不到
I can't.
不止是我俩的事
This is bigger than us.
将有无数的生命受到威胁
There are so many more lives at stake --
你们不会理解的  我做不到
You don't understand. I can't.
木已成舟
It's too late.
我...
I'm...
我怀孕了
I'm pregnant.
我们有麻烦了
Hey, we got a problem.
那些用血画的魔印 它们消失了
Those blood things, the sigils -- they're gone.
消失在
Gone as in...
我  我在后门上画了一个魔印
I-I drew one on the back of the door.
一转身
I turned around.
再看的时候就变成一块污点了
And when I looked back again, it was a smudge.
他说的没错
He's right.
圣油也没有了
There's no more holy oil.
你究竟是谁
Who the hell are you?
我是尤利尔
I'm Uriel.
哦  不会吧
Oh, come on.
快走
Go.
无路可退了
Here goes nothin'.
约翰
John!
萨姆
Sammy!
Sam!
我非常的抱歉
I'm really sorry.
安娜
Anna...
米迦勒
Michael.
Michael...
我不知道
...I didn't know.
再见  尤利尔
Goodbye, Uriel.
你把约翰怎么了
W-what did you do to John?
约翰没事
John is fine.
你是谁  你是什么
Who -- what are you?
这真是咱们之间迟来的谈话
Well, I'd say this conversation is long overdue,
-不是吗  - 治好他
- Wouldn't you?  - Fix him.
首先...
First...
咱们来谈谈
We talk.
然后我治好你那可爱的小萨姆
Then I fix your darling little Sammy.
你是怎么附身我爸爸的
How'd you get in my dad, anyway?
我告诉他我可以救他的妻子
I told him I could save his wife,
然后他就同意了
and he said yes.
看来是他们吹的太厉害了
I guess they oversold me
说我是你唯一的皮囊
Being your one and only vessel.
你的确是我的皮囊  但不是我唯一的
You're my true vessel but not my only one.
那是什么意思呢
What is that supposed to mean?
决定因素在于血统
It's a bloodline.
血统
A bloodline?
上溯到该隐和亚伯
Stretching back to Cain and Abel.
你有这样的血统  你父亲有这样的血统
It's in your blood, your father's blood,
这是你们家族的血统
Your family's blood.
真帅
Awesome.
天堂腌肉的命运锁链
Six degrees of heaven bacon.
你想要我怎么样
What do you want with me?
你当真不知道吗
You really don't know the answer to that?
你知道我不会同意你的附身
Well, you know I ain't gonna say yes,
为什么还要来这里
so why are you here?
你想把我怎么样
What do you want with me?!
我只是想让你明白
I just want you to understand
你和我必须完成的使命
what you and I have to do.
我知道了
Oh, I get it.
你对你的兄弟有一肚子牢骚
You got beef with your brother.
去接受心理治疗吧  老兄
Well, get some therapy, pal.
别来找我
Don't take it out on my planet!
你错了
You're wrong.
路西法违抗我们的父亲  背叛了我
Lucifer defied our father, and he betrayed me.
但是依然
But still...
就像你不愿杀死萨姆一样
I don't want this any more
我一点都不想这样做
than you would want to kill sam.
你知道  我的弟弟
You know, my brother --
实际上是我抚养他长大
I practically raised him.
我照顾他
I took care of him
用一种常人无法理解的方式
In a way most people could never understand,
并且我依然爱着他
and I still love him.
但是我会杀掉他
But I am going to kill him
因为那是正确的也是我必须做的
because it is right and I have to.
-因为是上帝的旨意  - 是的
- Oh, because god says so?  - Yes.
从一开始
From the beginning,
他就知道这件事将会怎样收场
he knew this was how it was going to end.
你会服从上帝的一切旨意吗
And you're just gonna do whatever god says.
因为我是个好儿子
Yes, because I am a good son.
好吧  相信我  老兄
Okay, well, trust me, pal.
过往经验告诉我
Take it from someone who knows --
这条路可走不通
That is a dead-end street.
你自以为比上帝看得更远吗
And you think you know better than my father?
不过是个渺小的人类
One unimportant little man --
凭什么认为自己可以自作主张
what makes you think you get to choose?
因为我相信  对于自己渺小的生活
Because I got to believe that I can choose what I do
我可以自己做主
with my... unimportant little life.
你错了
You're wrong.
知道为什么吗
You know how I know?
想想看  在万般巧合下
Think of a million random acts of chance
约翰和玛丽出生
that let John and Mary be born,
他们邂逅  相爱  并怀上你们
to meet, to fall in love, to have the two of you.
而又在万般机缘下  你所作出的选择
Think of the million random choices that you make --
从头到尾  自始至终
and yet how each and every one of them
只是令你更屈从于自身的命运
brings you closer to your destiny.
你知道为什么吗
Do you know why that is?
因为这不是什么巧合机缘  不是靠运气
Because it's not random. It's not chance.
这只是一局棋  不随他人意志而转移
It's a plan that is playing itself out perfectly.
什么自由意志不过你的错觉  迪恩
Free will's an illusion, Dean.
所以  你终究会答应我
That's why you're going to say yes.
得了
Oh, buck up.
没你想象得这么糟
It could be worse.
要知道  我和其他天使们不同
You know, unlike my brothers,
我对你可不会用烂就丢
I won't leave you a drooling mess when I'm done wearing you.
那我爸爸呢
Well, what about my dad?
完好无损
Better than new.
事实上  我还会帮你爸妈一个忙
In fact, I'm gonna do your mom and your dad a favor.
什么
What?
抹去他们的记忆
Scrub their minds.
他们什么也不会记得
They won't remember me or you.
你不能这样做
You can't do that.
我只是按她的意愿去做而已
I'm just giving your mother what she wants.
她会回到丈夫和家人身边
She can go back to her husband, her family --
这样一来她那天还是会去婴儿房
She's gonna walk right into that nursery!
自然
Obviously.
其实你早已明白  不论怎样
And you always knew that was going to play out
写好的剧本总会上演
one way or another.
你无法反抗上帝的意志
You can't fight city hall.
他回家了
He's home...
安然无恙
Safe and sound.
轮到你了
Your turn.
回见了  迪恩
I'll see you soon, Dean.
卡西迪奥
Castiel.
卡西  抱住你了
Cass! We got you.
见鬼的  你成功了
You son of a bitch. You made it.
我
I...
做到了吗
I did?
真是出乎意料
I'm very surprised.
喂喂喂  你没事的
Whoa! You're okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
快躺床上去
Bed? Yeah, yeah.
我要喝一杯
Well, I could use that drink now.
我也是
Yeah.
好吧
Well...
看看啊
This is it.
看什么
This is what?
自由意志三人组
Team free will.
一个有恶魔血瘾史的笨蛋
One ex-blood junkie,
一个在地狱为五斗米折腰的蠢材
One dropout with 6 bucks to his name,
再加上躺那儿昏迷不醒的糊涂天使
And Mr. Comatose over there.
酷毙了
It's awesome.
不好笑
It's not funny.
我又没笑
I'm not laughing.
大家都说我们会妥协
They all say we'll say yes.
就是  烦不烦啊
I know. It's getting annoying.
如果他们是对的怎么办
What if they're right?
没这回事
They're not.
我是说  我们中会有一个 ...
I mean, w-why -- why would we, either of us?
而
But...
我之前就曾妥协过
I've been weak before.
萨姆
Sam...
爸爸就答应了米迦勒
Michael got dad to say yes.
那不同
That was different.
那是因为安娜要杀了妈妈
Anna was about to kill mom.
如果你可以救她
And if you could save mom...
你会怎么做
What would you say?
你是从哪里弄来的
Where'd you even get it?
旧货清仓  只要25美分
Garage sale. 25 cents.
不管怎样  这还是挺欣慰的
Well, I'm glad to hear that, anyway.
我是说  你难道不觉得
I mean, you really don't think
这有点劣质吗
it's just a-a little cheesy?
我觉得很可爱
Mnh-mnh. I think it's sweet.
说不出理由
Can't even put my finger on why I like it.
我就是
I just...
就是很喜欢
Like it.
你喜欢我就喜欢
Well, then, I love it.
这一脚踢得真有劲
Quite a kick there.
在妈妈肚子里就这么调皮
Troublemaker already.
没事  我的宝贝儿
It's okay, baby. It's all okay.
有天使守护着你
Angels are watching over you.